# **DJURO ALFIREVIC**

Belgrade, Serbia djalfirevic@gmail.com +381 64 1 84 74 84

## Summary

Senior iOS Engineer with over 14 years in iOS development. Background includes iOS, macOS, .NET, Java, PHP, React and React Native development working in an Agile work environment. Complete iOS portfolio: <u>link</u>. Personal website: <u>link</u>.

# **Key Skills**

Languages/technologies/frameworks: Objective-C, Swift, React, React Native, Java, .NET, C#, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Agile, Scrum, Git

## **Work Experience**

Reddit: iOS Lead @ Profiles

October 2021 -

- Working as an iOS Lead

## Lolly: Director of Engineering / iOS Lead

October 2020 - October 2021

- Working as a Director of Engineering
- Working as an iOS Lead

#### Medable: iOS Chief Architect

October 2019 - October 2020

- Working as a iOS Chief Architect

### **Symphony: Senior Software Engineer**

October 2017 - June 2019

- Designed and developed iOS/macOS/React/React Native applications
- Worked as a Team Lead and Expert Interviewer

#### **Cubes: Senior Software Engineer / CTO**

September 2015 - September 2017

- Worked as an iOS instructor
- Worked as a Software Engineering Manager/Project Manager/CTO

# Ministry of Defense: Senior Software Engineer September 2006 - August 2015

- Worked on full software development lifecycle (.NET, Java)
- Worked as a Chief Software Architect

## **Education**

Masters Degree 2001 - 2006

Military Academy, MSc Software Engineering